{
	"saymyname": [
        {
            "Question": "Arnold Schwarzeneggar Has Been Used As A Hotel Pseudonym By This Celebrity",
            "Answer": "George Clooney",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Charged Chambers And Birds’ Nests Are Two Euphimisms For The Female Genitals As Penned By This Man",
            "Answer": "William Shakespeare",
        },
        {
            "Question": "J. C. Penney Has Been Used As A Hotel Pseudonym By This Celebrity",
            "Answer": "Bono",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Lord Greystoke, Aka Tarzan Has Been Used As A Hotel Pseudonym By This Celebrity",
            "Answer": "Marlon Brando",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Memoirs Of A Woman Of Pleasure Is A 1748 Erotic Novel Also Known By This Name",
            "Answer": "Fanny Hill",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Miss Lollipop Has Been Used As A Hotel Pseudonym By This Celebrity",
            "Answer": "Angelina Jolie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Some Like It Hot Was Originally Titled",
            "Answer": "Not Tonight, Josephine",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tinkerbell Has Been Used As A Hotel Pseudonym By This Celebrity",
            "Answer": "Paris Hilton",
        },
        {
            "Question": "50 Cent’s Miniature Schnauzer Is Named",
            "Answer": "Oprah Winfrey",
        },
        {
            "Question": "7-Up Was Originally Called",
            "Answer": "Bib-label Lithiated Lemon-lime Soda",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Music Video That Captures The Bridal Party And Wedding Guests Singing Along To Well-Known Songs Is Called A",
            "Answer": "Marryoke",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Swedish Couple Was Fined 5,000 Kronor For Naming Their Child",
            "Answer": "Brfxxccxxmnpcccclllmmnprxvclmnckssqlbb11116",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Well Known South Korean Olympic Pole Vaulter",
            "Answer": "Kim Yoo-suk",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Alice, The 3Rd-Largest Town In Australia’s Northern Territory, Used To Be Called",
            "Answer": "Stuart",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Although Her Husband Is Not A Fan Of It, Kate Beckinsale Has Used This Pseudonym At Hotels",
            "Answer": "Sigourney Beaver",
        },
        {
            "Question": "At Last Count, There Are 99 Lakes In Minnesota Named",
            "Answer": "Mud Lake",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bank Of America Was Originally Called",
            "Answer": "Bank Of Italy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Because Its Residents Couldn’t Agree On One, This Is The Official Name Of A Town In Tennessee",
            "Answer": "Difficult",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bill Clinton’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Eagle",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bob Dole’s Secret-Service Codename",
            "Answer": "Ramrod",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Buzz Aldrin’s Mother’s Maiden Name Was",
            "Answer": "Moon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cary Grant’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Archibald Alexander Leach",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Charles Barkley Entered The Basketball League With This Nickname",
            "Answer": "Round Mound Of Rebound",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Charlie Sheen’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Carlos Irwin Estevez",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Chevy Chase’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Cornelius Crane Chase",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Christina Aguilera Owns Two Papillons Named Chewy And",
            "Answer": "Stinky",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Demi Moore’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Demetria Guynes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dido’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Florian Cloud De Bounevialle Armstrong",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dr. Seuss Was Born As",
            "Answer": "Theodor Geisel",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ellis Island And Liberty Island Were Once Known As",
            "Answer": "Little Oyster And Big Oyster",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Elton John’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Reginald Kenneth Dwight",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Elvis Had A Pet Monkey Named",
            "Answer": "Scatter",
        },
        {
            "Question": "First Used The Letter ‘U’ As An Abbreviation For ‘You’",
            "Answer": "William Shakespeare",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Friends And Family Cover A Woman With Spoiled Eggs, Molasses, And Other Items During A Scottish Ritual Called",
            "Answer": "Blackening The Bride",
        },
        {
            "Question": "George W. Bush’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Trailblazer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Google Was Originally Called",
            "Answer": "Backrub",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Harry Houdini’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Ehrich Weiss",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Henry Kissinger’s Secret-Service Codename",
            "Answer": "Woodcutter",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Idaho Derives From The Kowa-Apache (Athabaskan) Word Idaahe, Meaning",
            "Answer": "Enemy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In 1971, This Man Brought A Case To The Western Distrcit Court Of Pennsylvania Against Satan",
            "Answer": "Gerard Mayo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In 2003, The World’s Number 15 Female Tennis Player Was",
            "Answer": "Anna Smashnova",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In 2010, The Rsc Brought Romeo And Juliet Into The Digital Age With An Improvised Series Of Twitter Exchanges, Titled",
            "Answer": "Such Tweet Sorrow",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In The 2009 Formula One Season, 12% Of Grand Prix Drivers Were Named",
            "Answer": "Sebastian",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In The Dutch Version Of Clue, Professor Plum Is Called",
            "Answer": "Professor Pimpel",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In The Mid To Late 1700’S, The Annual Listing Of London Prostitutes Was Called",
            "Answer": "Harris’s List Of Covent Garden Ladies",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Iowa Was Named After The Natives Of The Chiwere Branch Of The Aiouan Family, From Dakota Ayusxba, Meaning",
            "Answer": "Sleepy Ones",
        },
        {
            "Question": "James Bond Was Originally Going To Be Called",
            "Answer": "James Secretan",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Joaquin Phoenix’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Joaquin Rafael Bottom",
        },
        {
            "Question": "John F. Kennedy’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Lancer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "John Legend’s English Bulldog Is Called",
            "Answer": "Puddy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "John Mccain’s Secret-Service Codename",
            "Answer": "Phoenix",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Karenna Gore’s Secret-Service Codename",
            "Answer": "Smurfette",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Karl And Jenny Marx Named All Four Of Their Daughters",
            "Answer": "Jenny",
        },
        {
            "Question": "King Herod’s First Wife Was Named",
            "Answer": "Doris",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Lady Macbeth’s First Name",
            "Answer": "Gruoch",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Laurel And Hardy Are Known As This In Germany",
            "Answer": "Dick And Doof",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Lucille Ball’s Two Dogs Were Called",
            "Answer": "Tinker Toy And Whoopee",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mariah Carey’s Dog Is Called",
            "Answer": "Jackson P. Mutley",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Medieval French Patron Saint Of Ham",
            "Answer": "St. Jambon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Medieval French Patron Saint Of Talkative Women",
            "Answer": "St. Coquette",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Melbourne Used To Be Called",
            "Answer": "Batmania",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Michelle Obama’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Renaissance",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mickey Rooney’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Joseph Yule Jr.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Minnesota Is Named For The River, From Dakota (Siouan) Mnisota, Meaning",
            "Answer": "Cloudy Water, Milky Water",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Minnie Driver’s Dog Is Named",
            "Answer": "Bubba",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Nachos Were Invented By A Man Called",
            "Answer": "Nacho",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Nancy Reagan’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Rainbow",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Newt Gingrich’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "T-rex",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Patented A Fragrant Brassiere In 1998",
            "Answer": "Chin-tang Chen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Patented A Naval Lint Removing Pick In 1982",
            "Answer": "Larry M. Belcher",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Patented A Scented Doll With The Appearance Of An Old Person",
            "Answer": "Ethel Hidalgo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Patented An Apparatus To Pat Yourself On The Back",
            "Answer": "Ralph R. Pire",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Patented An Athletic Shoe With An Attached Small Basketball Hoop On The Heel",
            "Answer": "Gregg A. Myles",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pepsi Was Originally Called",
            "Answer": "Brad’s Drink",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Popeye Has Four Nephews Named Pipeye, Peepeye, Pupeye, And",
            "Answer": "Poopeye",
        },
        {
            "Question": "President Aquino Of The Philippines Has Two Sisters Called",
            "Answer": "Pinksy And Ballsy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "President Aquino Of The Philippines Is Called This Locally",
            "Answer": "Noynoy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "President Obama’ Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Renegade",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Rachel Griffiths And Andrew Taylor Named Their Son",
            "Answer": "Banjo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Red Bull Was Originally Called This",
            "Answer": "Red Water Buffalo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ron Nessen’s Secret-Service Codename",
            "Answer": "Clam Chowder",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ron Ziegler’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Whale Boat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ronald Reagan’s Pet Name For Nancy Reagan Was",
            "Answer": "Mommy Poo Pants",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ronald Reagan’s Secret-Service Nickname",
            "Answer": "Rawhide",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sarah Palin’s Secret-Service Codename",
            "Answer": "Denali",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Shania Twain’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Eileen Regina Edwards",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Simon And Garfunkel Were Originally Called",
            "Answer": "Tom And Jerry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Singer Wayne Newton Is A Descendant Of",
            "Answer": "Pocahontas",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Stevie Wonder’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Steveland Judkins",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The 1999 President Of Niger",
            "Answer": "Major Wanke",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Ad / Bc Dating System Was Devised By A Monk Called",
            "Answer": "Dennis The Small",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Bird With The Largest Vocabulary Who Knew 1,728 Words Was Named",
            "Answer": "Puck The Budgie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Cartoon Strip Peanuts Is Known As This In Denmark",
            "Answer": "Radishes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Crunch Of A Pickle Should Be Audible Form 10 Paces According To This Group",
            "Answer": "Pickle Packers International",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Film Jaws Was Based On A Novel By Peter Benchley, Whose Father Suggested The Title",
            "Answer": "What’s That Noshin’ On Ma Leg?",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The First Ad For A Personal Vibrator Appeared In 1899 In This Magazine",
            "Answer": "Mcclure’s",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The First Circus Performer To Be Shot Out Of A Canon At Fourteen Years Old",
            "Answer": "Rosa “zazel” Richter",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The First Film To Show The Act Of Sex In 1932 Was",
            "Answer": "Extase",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The First Manager Of The First Mcdonald’s Franchise Was Called",
            "Answer": "Ed Macluckie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Founder Of United Airlines Had A Pet Pekingese Called",
            "Answer": "General Motors",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Full Name Of Jamie Oliver And Juliette Norton’s Second Daughter",
            "Answer": "Daisy Boo Pamela Oliver",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Full Name Of Jamie Oliver And Juliette Norton’s Youngest Child",
            "Answer": "Buddy Bear Maurice Oliver",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Game Simon Says Was Originall Called",
            "Answer": "Do This, Do That",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hand Jive Was Invented At A Club In London Called",
            "Answer": "The Cat Whiskers",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Last Private Resident Of 10 Downing Street Was Named",
            "Answer": "Mr. Chicken",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Longest Name Of A Place In The Uk With No Repeated Letters",
            "Answer": "Bricklehampton",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Man Who Takes Care Of Vips In The Presidential Guest House In Washington Dc Is Named",
            "Answer": "Randy Bumgardner",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Name Of Lil’ Kim’s Daughter Is",
            "Answer": "Royal Reign",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Name Of The First Woman To Run The 400-Meter Hurdles In Under 53 Seconds",
            "Answer": "Marina Stepanova",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Name Of The Second Son Of Alex O’loughlin And Malia Jones",
            "Answer": "Lion",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Oldest Living Thing On Earth Is A Bristlecone Pine Over 4,500 Years Old Named",
            "Answer": "Methuselah",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Only Female Pharaoh Of Egypt",
            "Answer": "Hatshepsut",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Pap Smear Is Named After This U.S. Pathologist",
            "Answer": "Dr. George N. Papanicolaou",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Patron Saint Of Oversleeping Is Called",
            "Answer": "St. Vitus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Patron Saint Of Salmon Who Died Of Shock After Getting Into A Hot Bath",
            "Answer": "St. Mungo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Second-Largest Lake In Bolivia Is Called",
            "Answer": "Lake Poop",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Secret-Service Codename For Antonio Banderas",
            "Answer": "Zorro",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Secret-Service Codename For Pope John Paul Ii",
            "Answer": "Halo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Secret-Service Codename Used For Ted Kennedy",
            "Answer": "Sunburn",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Son Of Jason Lee And Beth Riesgraf Is",
            "Answer": "Pilot Inspektor",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Two Most Popular Dog Names In Russia Are",
            "Answer": "Blackie And Breezy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Two Secret-Service Codenames For Prince Charles Are ‘Principal’ And",
            "Answer": "Unicorn",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The World’s First Female Interactive Sex Robot Is Called",
            "Answer": "Roxxxy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The World’s First Male Interactive Sex Robot Is Named",
            "Answer": "Rocky",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Zip Code 20252 Belongs To",
            "Answer": "Smokey The Bear",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Theresa Berkley Was A 19Th-Century English Dominatrix Who Designed A Flogging Rack Called",
            "Answer": "The Berkley Horse",
        },
        {
            "Question": "These Are The Four Male Names Least Likely To Be Clicked On By Women On Dating Websites",
            "Answer": "Dennis, Kevin, Justin, Marvin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "These Siamese Twins Were Married And Fathered Twenty-Two Chidlren Between The Two Of Them",
            "Answer": "Chang And Eng",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Thirty Thousand Hawaiians Signed A Petition To Change Maui’s Name To",
            "Answer": "Gilligan’s Island",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Actor Once Played With His Band At A Krispy Kreme Doughbuts Branch Opening",
            "Answer": "Bruce Willis",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Artist’s Greatest-Hits Album Contained 40 Minutes Of Silence, Followed By Applause",
            "Answer": "Marcel Marceau",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Author Always Carried A Compass So He Could Sleep Facing North",
            "Answer": "Charles Dickens",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Carthaginian Leader Took An Oath Of Hatred Against The Romans At Nine Years Old",
            "Answer": "Hannibal",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Celebrity Got Her Nickname From Childood Flatulence",
            "Answer": "Whoopi Goldberg",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This City In Mongolia Is The Coldest National Capital",
            "Answer": "Ulaanbaatar",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Founder Of Zen Buddhism Spent Nine Years Sitting Facing A Wall",
            "Answer": "Bodhidharma",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Goat Was Once Elected As The Mayor Of Lijitas, Texas",
            "Answer": "Clay Henry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Is A Disorder Found In Southeast Asia In Which A Man Believes That His Penis Is Shrinking And Will Soon Disappear",
            "Answer": "Koro",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Is The Longest Name In The Bible",
            "Answer": "Mahershalalhashbaz",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Is The Name Of Your Second Toe If It’s Bigger Than Your Big Toe",
            "Answer": "Morton’s Toe",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Is The Term Given To Women Who Attend Rodeos With The Intent To Sleep With One Of The Cowboys",
            "Answer": "Buckle Bunnies",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Judge Was Known For Taking A Nap And Knitting During Court Sessions",
            "Answer": "Lord Thankerton",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This King Of Tonga In The 1700S Made It His Royal Duty To Sleep With Every Virgin Woman In His Kingdom",
            "Answer": "Fatafehi Paulaho",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Man Invented The Lawnmower And The Adjustable Wrench",
            "Answer": "Edwin Beard Budding",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Mongol Ruler Had 5,000 Dogs",
            "Answer": "Kublai Khan",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Musician Once Proposed To Marie Antoinette",
            "Answer": "Mozart",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Roman Emperor Invented A Whoopee Cushion, Which He Used At Dinner Parties.",
            "Answer": "Elagabalus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Was The Name Of President Mckinley’s Pet Parrot",
            "Answer": "Washington Post",
        },
        {
            "Question": "This Was The Nickname Of Richard The Lionheart’s Little Brother",
            "Answer": "Dollheart",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tim Patch, The Australian Artist Who Paints Landscapes And Portraits With His Penis, Often Goes By His Stage Name,",
            "Answer": "Pricasso",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Time Magazine’s Man Of The Year In 1952",
            "Answer": "Queen Elizabeth Ii",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tina Fey’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Elizabeth Stamatina Fey",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tom And Jerry Were Originally Called",
            "Answer": "Jasper And Jinx",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Was Offered Passport Number 007 But Turned It Down",
            "Answer": "Margaret Thatcher",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Was President Of The Isle Of Man Basking Shark Society",
            "Answer": "Olivia Newton-john",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Was The Roman Goddess Of Sewers",
            "Answer": "Cloacina",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Washington State Was Named For President George Washington, Whose Surname In Old English Means",
            "Answer": "Estate Of A Man Named Wassa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Waterskiing Was Called This In The 1880S",
            "Answer": "Plankgliding",
        },
        {
            "Question": "West Side Story Was Originally Called",
            "Answer": "East Side Story",
        },
        {
            "Question": "What Animated Character Got His Name From The Word Pine Nut In Italian?",
            "Answer": "Pinocchio",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Wild Bill Hickok’s Brother Was Nicknamed",
            "Answer": "Tame Bill Hickok",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Woody Allen’s Real Name",
            "Answer": "Allen Konigsberg",
        }
    ]
}